<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<AntMovieCatalog Format="35" Version="3.5.0 (2005-05-29)" Date="23.01.2006 9:56:00">
 <Catalog>
  <Properties Owner="Ivan" Mail="ivan@movies.nnov.ru" Site="http://www.movies.nnov.ru"/>
  <Contents>
   <Movie Number="1" Checked="True" Date="04.11.2004" Rating="7.0" OriginalTitle="Alice 'in' Wonderland" TranslatedTitle="Алиса в стране чудес" FormattedTitle="Alice in Wonderland (Алиса в стране чудес)" Director="Clyde Geronimi, Wilfred Jackson" Country="USA" Category="Animation" Year="1951" Length="74" Actors="Kathryn Beaumont (as Alice (voice)), Ed Wynn (as Mad Hatter (voice)), Richard Haydn (as Caterpillar (voice)), Sterling Holloway (as Cheshire Cat (voice)), Jerry Colonna (as March Hare (voice)), Verna Felton (as Queen of Hearts (voice)), J. Pat O&#39;Malley (as Walrus-Carpenter/Dee and Dum/ (voice)), Bill Thompson (I) (as White Rabbit, Dodo (voice)), Heather Angel (as Alice&#39;s sister (voice)), Joseph Kearns (I) (as Doorknob (voice)), Larry Grey (as Bill (voice)), Queenie Leonard (as Bird in the Tree (voice)), Dink Trout (as King of Hearts (voice)), Doris Lloyd (as The Rose (voice)), James MacDonald (II) (as Dormouse (voice))" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Title?0043274" Description="Убежав из дома, Алиса увидела под старой яблоней большого белого Кролика, одетого в куртку и жилет. Достав из кармана часы, Кролик торопливо скрылся в подозрительно темной норе. Набравшись смелости, Алиса шагнула вслед за ним... и попала в чудесный сказочный мир, где сбываются самые несбыточные фантазии. Чтобы попасть обратно домой, Алисе придется совершить путешествие через весь этот странный и причудливый мир, в котором ее поджидают совершенно невероятные приключения и совершенно фантастические существа... Добро пожаловать в Страну Чудес." Comments="If there&#39;s one thing that most people remember about Alice In Wonderland then it must be this version of the film!||Alice In Wonderland is just great, and this Disney version is the one thing that sticks in my mind. The animation may not be a landmark and it isn&#39;t very true to the original story (it&#39;s a shame that not everything is included) but it&#39;s been given that certain Disney magic which just grips you! It&#39;s the kind of story that can only really be shown by animation.||So strong is the Disney version of the film that one day I told a friend that I was getting something for my sister to do with Alice In Wonderland. She replied &#39;Is your sister really into Disney?&#39;.||The one thing I really love though is how someone can just write a whole load of complete and utter rubbish, mix it together by calling it &#39;wonderland&#39;, turn up the curiosity and have it enjoyed my millions of people around the world! I still watch it at times as it&#39;s so enjoyable seeing this complete fantasy world where anything could happen! It&#39;s just a shame that Alice&#39;s adventure ends so quickly!||My rating - 7 out of 1 " VideoFormat="DivX 5" VideoBitrate="1877" AudioFormat="AC3/AC3" AudioBitrate="768" Resolution="512x384" Framerate="25" Languages="Закадровый перевод актерский,English" Size="699+701" Disks="2" Picture="Covers\AliceXinXWonderland.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="2" Checked="True" Date="24.03.2004" Rating="6.0" OriginalTitle="Bring 'It' On" TranslatedTitle="Добейся успеха / Заводилы" FormattedTitle="Bring It On (Добейся успеха / Заводилы)" Director="Peyton Reed" Country="USA" Category="Comedy" Year="2000" Length="89" Actors="Kirsten Dunst (as Torrance Shipman), Eliza Dushku (as Missy Pantone), Jesse Bradford (as Cliff Pantone), Gabrielle Union (as Isis &#39;Ice), Clare Kramer (as Courtney), Nicole Bilderback (as Whitney), Tsianina Joelson (as Darcy), Rini Bell (as Kasey), Nathan West (as Jan), Huntley Ritter (as Les), Shamari Fears (as Lava), Natina Reed (as Jenelope), Brandi Williams (as Lafred), Richard Hillman (as Aaron), Lindsay Sloane (as Big Red)" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Tsearch?title=Bring+It+On" Description="В Америке ни один футбольный матч не обходится без команды поддержки, набранной из самых сексапильных и подвижных девиц. А стать капитаном - мечта любой девчонки в школе или университете. И вот выбор падает на Торренс. Ее парень Эрон скоро уезжает в колледж, и она надеется попасть в тот же колледж, чтобы ее таланты пригодились и там. Эта молодежная комедия рассказывает о том, как идет борьба команд поддержки из разных университетов за победу в национальном чемпионате, и в этой борьбе все средства хороши. Ну а без любви молодежных комедий на бывает. Если будете смотреть, отключайте мозги.  (Иванов М.)" Comments="I am not going to make any excuses. This was an excellent film for all ages. So many of the positive reviews I have seen prior to this one have had to make disclaimers (e.g. yes, it was childish...) but I will not do so. I am going to be confident in the intelligence of anyone reading this to understand that the quality of a film always has to be taken in the context it was meant to be viewed in. Bring It On is an excellent farce making fun of The Stereotypical Cheerleader. At the same time, the characters were very real, well played, and easy to empathize with. The movement (dance?) was lots of fun to watch. I also felt that the characters were much more realistic than many teenage characters are usually portrayed in film - more sarcastic and intelligently witty and sexual than usual. I think this is good, because many films give the impression that all teenagers are naive and childish, when in fact this is not necessarily the case. I must admit though that I couldn&#39;t help thinking that certain things had to happen the way they did for the sake of Political Correctness, and that is disappointing, but from the filmmakers perspective understandable. It was good to see a little bit of gay-friendliness in the film, which is rare to find in any films.||Overall, I thought it was a lot of fun and I left the film feeling good " VideoFormat="DivX 3.11 Low Motion" VideoBitrate="961" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="128" Resolution="640x360" Framerate="24,029" Languages="Закадровый перевод 1 голос,English" Size="693" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\BringXItXOnXXengX.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="3" Checked="True" Date="20.11.2001" Rating="6.0" OriginalTitle="6th Day, 'The'" TranslatedTitle="6ой день" FormattedTitle="6th Day, The (6ой день)" Director="Roger Spottiswoode" Country="USA" Category="Action" Year="2000" Length="123" Actors="Arnold Schwarzenegger (as Adam Gibson), Michael Rapaport (as Hank Morgan), Tony Goldwyn (as Michael Drucker), Michael Rooker (as Robert Marshall), Sarah Wynter (I) (as Talia Elsworth), Wendy Crewson (as Natalie Gibson), Rodney Rowland (as P. Wiley (as Rod Rowland)), Terry Crews (I) (as Vincent), Ken Pogue (as Speaker Day), Colin Cunningham (I) (as Tripp), Robert Duvall (as Dr. Griffin Weir), Wanda Cannon (as Katherine Weir), Taylor Anne Reid (as Clara Gibson), Jennifer Gareis (as Virtual Girlfriend), Don McManus (I) (as RePet Salesman)" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Tsearch?title=6th+Day%2C+The+%282000%29" Description="В начале третьего тысячелетия самым суровым законом стал &#34;закон Шестого дня&#34;. Он запрещал клонирование людей и создание искусственных копий человека. Но огромная подпольная империя вопреки запрету выращивает человечество нового будущего, сонмы управляемых теней. Налаженная машина преступления не давала сбоев, пока в ее совершенный механизм не вмешалась случайность: пилот вертолета Адам Гибсон неожиданно приоткрыл непроницаемую завесу заговора. Теперь он - последний рубеж обороны, отделяющий цивилизацию от общества зомби" Comments="THE 6TH DAY / (2000) **** (out of four) ||By Blake French:||	Roger Spottiswoode&#39;s recent action film &#34;The 6th Day&#34; is of the best thrillers you will see this year, and possibly the next. Seldom do action pictures have as much thought, insight, and are this well written and developed. With a screenplay by Cormac Wibberley and Marianne Wibberley, the movie takes one of the most controversial current subjects, cloning, and applies it to a time when it may cause discern for public, the near future. This is a movie with ample prominence and proximity, and depending where you stand on the issue of cloning will determine whether or not we will side with the main character here. He is played by Arnold Schwarzenegger, now forgiven for his last several bombs, &#34;Jingle all the Way,&#34; &#34;End of Days,&#34; and &#34;Batman and Robin.&#34; If one thriller can make up for those three hideous productions, you know it must be very good...and it is.||	Schwarzenegger stars as Adam Gibson, a middle-aged everyman who has a lovely wife, Natalie (Wendy Crewson), and a young, pretty daughter named Carla (Taylor Anne Reid). Adam and his friend, Hank (Michael Rapaport), are pilots for the Double X Charter Company, a helicopter touring service. While most of society has adapted to the advancements in technology, such as the ability to clone deceased pets and to own a realistic looking and behaving doll, Adam is pretty old-fashioned when it comes branch of knowledge. At least until one night when he returns home to find his family and friends celebrating his birthday with him already inside. Outside his house waits several agents, including Talia (Sarah Wynter), Robert (Michael Rooker), and Vincent (Terry Crews), who attempt to kill him. ||	Adam and Hank were cloned by a multi-billion dollar food cloning company, Replacement Technologies. This corporation is run by an individual named Drucker (Tony Goldwyn), who supposedly used his cloning equipment to replenish the world&#39;s food supply. While human cloning is illegal, he and his chief scientist, Dr. Weir (Robert DuVall), are constantly cloning for various reasons. After they discover Adam escaped his assassins, they begin an all out scheme to destroy the evidence in which they have created. ||	The tedious measures the filmmakers take in development of the characters, situations, events, and motives are outstanding. We get to know the main characters. They are intriguing and the conflict is highly engrossing&#39; even the antagonist&#39;s motives provoke thought. The film is engaging throughout because the subject and its execution are so relevant and controversial. &#34;The 6th Day&#34; does not feel like a high tech action film, although it is. But it also has a very authentic flavor because it uses the special effects to further the story, and the action sequences are all in context of the plot. ||	About those action scenes and special effects, they do not distract from the movie&#39;s themes or story. Roger Spottiswoode, whose most poplar work consists of  &#34;Tomorrow Never Dies,&#34; (1997) and &#34;Turner &#38; Hooch,&#34; (1989), keeps the story fast-paced but finely focused. The futuristic material, so often overused in movies nowadays, is kept to a believable realm here. The film handles the material with delicacy&#34; if the movie was to use too little, its subject matter would be unconvincing&#34; if there was too much, then the film would become too far-fetched. Spottiswoode contrasts just the right amount, and blends the effects with the various character&#39;s personalities beautifully. ||	What impresses me most of all about movies like &#34;The 6th Day&#34; is how the writers deny the urge to allow the special effects and action to take place of the passion in characters. In the year 2000, we received big waves in &#34;The Perfect Storm,&#34; big explosions in &#34;U-571,&#34; computer animated sequences in &#34;X-Men,&#34; and all sorts of special martial arts stunts in &#34;Charlie&#39;s Angels&#34; and &#34;Legend of Drunken Master.&#34; But what those movies were missing is depth and insight of the real world, and the movies that did contain heart, like &#34;The Perfect Storm,&#34; were contrived and shameless. With &#34;The 6th Day&#34; we have a movie that contains all the excitement and special effects, but within a story that is character-based and relevant to our times. This is one of the top ten movies released in the year 2000 " VideoFormat="DivX 3.11 Low Motion" VideoBitrate="628" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="128" Resolution="496x208" Framerate="25" Languages="Перевод,English отдельно" Size="682" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\6th.Day.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="4" Checked="True" Date="20.11.2001" Rating="5.0" OriginalTitle="Art of War, The" TranslatedTitle="Искуство войны" FormattedTitle="Art of War, The (Искуство войны)" Director="Christian Duguay (I)" Country="Canada" Category="Action" Year="2000" Length="117" Actors="Wesley Snipes (as Neil Shaw), Anne Archer (as Eleanor Hooks), Maury Chaykin (as Capella), Marie Matiko (as Julia Fang), Cary-Hiroyuki Tagawa (as David Chan), Michael Biehn (as Robert Bly), Donald Sutherland (as U.N. Secretary General Douglas Thomas), Liliana Komorowska (as Novak), James Hong (as Ambassador Wu), Paul Hopkins (I) (as Ray), Glen Chin (as Ochai), Ron Yuan (as Ming), Bonnie Mak (as Anna), Uni Park (as Tina Chan), Erin Selby (as Hong Kong Reporter)" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Title?0160009" Description="Гонконг празднует новое тысячелетие, новый Китай, а в это время дружная команда скачивает из компьютеров важную информацию. Среди гостей и Уэсли Снайпс работающий вместе с нарушителями. Они организуют телефонный звонок министру обороны и одновременно на огромном телеэкране показывают министра, занимающегося любовью с девочкой 12 - 13 лет. Снайпс говорит министру, что в прошлом месяце тот взял 90 миллионов долларов и с помощью ООН направил их на новые ракетные технологии, а деньги предназначались для голодающих и жертвам наводнения. От министра требуют, чтобы он снова сел за стол переговоров с Южной Кореей. Увидев на экране скаченные с компьтеров данные по ракетным технологиям, министр соглашается. В тот же момент он отдает приказ поймать нарушителя. Проявляя чудеса владения боевыми искусствами, Снайпс покидает новогодний прием, прыгнув с крыши небоскреба с парашютом. В следующей сцене генерального секретаря ООН (Сазерлэнд) спрашивают, как удалось достичь вернуть Северную Корею к мирным переговорам. Проходит 6 месяцев. Снайпс оказывается Нейлом Шоу, сверхсекретным и лучшим агентом специального отдела в ООН. Рана, полученная в предыдущем задании, заживает, и приходит пора нового задания. В купленном китайцами отеле посол Китая устраивает большой прием в честь нового американо-китайского торгового договора. Среди гостей генеральный секретарь ООН и... Нейл Шоу. Девушка из группы Нейла незаметно прикрепляет послу &#34;жучка&#34;. Говорят о важности открытия двери для торговли с Китаем, а из будки для переводчицы раздается выстрел, и посол падает с дыркой во лбу. Шоу гонится за снайпером - погоня снята захватывающе - переговариваясь с агентом Блайтом, но потом выбегает на улицу, где обычные полицейские приказывают ему бросить оружие и положить руки за голову. Шоу не может сказать, где и кем он работает, и попадает в руки ФБР. Во время перевозки на машину ФБР совершается налет, а Шоу вывозят какие-то китайцы с явной целью убить, да так, чтобы и следа не осталось. Но не на того ребята нарвались. Шоу приходит в себя и уничтожает часть своих похитителей. Нет смысла персказывать дальнейшие события. Для затравки я уже итак немало рассказал. Суть сюжета сводится к тому, что Шоу должен снять с себя подозрение в убийстве, найти настоящего убийцу и разобраться с триадами, а для этого ему придется применить все свое &#34;искусство&#34; войны.||Это классный, высокотехничный боевик, отличное развлечение для любителей боевиков в ранге блокбастера.  (Иванов М.)" Comments="THE ART OF WAR / (2000) ** (out of four)||By Blake French:||	The Art of War refers to an ancient handbook by a mighty Asian general named Sun Tsu, who hypothesized that wars can be won without physical combat. Numerous powerful leaders, including Napoleon, defeated their enemies by using the ideas of Sun Tsu. According to the action flick &#34;The Art of War,&#34; Tsu&#39;s theories apply to the world of business and politics as they do to war.||&#34;It&#39;s about strategy, manipulation and control, all the way through,&#34; says director Christian Duguay, whose credits include TV&#39;s &#34;Joan of Arc,&#34; and &#34;The Assignment.&#34; &#34;The whole film is based on the theme of manipulation and the idea that things are not what they appear. That&#39;s what I think makes this film very unique and exciting.&#34;||Or how about confusing and hard to follow, better words to describe what Christian calls &#34;one character manipulating the other, who is manipulating still another.&#34; The production notes inform us on the ancient techniques and strategy of manipulation, but &#34;The Art of War&#34; is not the movie to justify those principles. After half a dozen plot twists, even more action sequences, and probably more hidden character motives, this film becomes exactly what Tsu condemned: the actual fighting of war. There&#39;s enough action in this movie to classify it as a mixture of material arts and a James Bond, but after one perplexing situation after another, we simply toss our arms and stop caring altogether. ||Instead of a plot description, let&#39;s examine the sources of this movie&#39;s recycled story. First, we get a man who is wrongfully accused for a murder he did not commit. In a strike of luck and personal investigation, he gets the chance to prove himself innocent after escaping from the police during a transportation accident. Yes, that sounds like &#34;The Fugitive.&#34; Now throw in the film&#39;s follow up &#34;U.S. Marshals,&#34; about an accused government agent using his insider knowledge while an Asian thug tracks him down. Combine the two similar plots and you get something like &#34;The Art of War,&#34; straight from the recycling plant to your personal viewing pleasure.||Working with a forty-million dollar budget, Snipes himself performs many of his own stunts and combat sequences. The film does offer some exciting, if conventional, action sequences, but I wanted a smart plot about political tactics and clever espionage, not run-of-the-mill action. Anne Archer and Maury Chaykin contribute effective performances as the villains, and Snipes does good things with his character. But the plot just doesn&#39;t work. It houses too many characters, too many plot complications, and too much technical government stuff. &#34;The Art of War&#34;  is pretty much an unimaginative telling of a tale we&#39;ve already heard " VideoFormat="DivX 3.11 Low Motion" VideoBitrate="563" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="96" Resolution="720x272" Framerate="23,98" Languages="Russian,English отдельно" Size="588" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\ArtXOfXWarXXengX.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="5" Checked="True" Date="22.11.2001" Rating="6.0" OriginalTitle="Cell, The" TranslatedTitle="Клетка" FormattedTitle="Cell, The (Клетка)" Director="Tarsem Singh" Country="USA" Category="Sci-Fi" Year="2000" Length="107" Actors="Jennifer Lopez (as Catherine Deane), Colton James (as Edward Baines), Dylan Baker (as Henry West), Marianne Jean-Baptiste (as Dr. Miriam Kent), Gerry Becker (as Dr. Barry Cooperman), Musetta Vander (as Ella Baines), Patrick Bauchau (as Lucien Baines), Vincent D&#39;Onofrio (as Carl Rudolph Stargher), Catherine Sutherland (I) (as Anne Marie Vicksey), Vince Vaughn (as FBI Agent Peter Novak), James Gammon (I) (as FBI Agent Teddy Lee), Jake Weber (as FBI Special Agent Gordon Ramsey), Dean Norris (as FBI Agent Cole), Tara Subkoff (as Julia Hickson), Lauri Johnson (as Mrs. Hickson)" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Title?0209958" Description="Сексапильная Дженнифер Лопес в фантастическом триллере &#34;Клетка&#34;.|Карл (Винсент д&#39;Онофрио), маньяк- психопат, он бросает женщин в стеклянную клетку и снимает на видео, как постоянно текущая с потолка вода за 40 часов наполняет клетку до краев и уже помешавшаяся  рассудком жертва захлебывается. По всему телу маньяка вживлены стальные кольца, за которые он подвешивает себя цепями, и в таком виде просматривает отснятый материал. Арестовать его крайне сложно, но после очередного похищения полиции повезло, маньяк схвачен. Однако у него начинается шизофренический припадок после которого он впадает в кому. Времени остается все меньше, а местонахождение девушки неизвестно.|И тут появляется Кэтрин (Дженифер Лопес) врач психолог обладающая уникальной методикой проникновения в подсознание пациентов находящихся в коме. Только она может узнать, где искать девушку. Используя свои способности, Кэтрин погружается в странный, завораживающий, не имеющий ничего общего с реальной жизнью, мир маньяка. Но в этом мире, созданным воображением извращенца все законы подчиняются только своему хозяину. В этот мир легко попасть, но выбраться из него почти невозможно. Теперь опасность угрожает и психологу." Comments="I&#39;ve said before that some films are like `nothing you have ever seen before&#39;. Well, The Cell takes that saying and burns it down, blows it up and drowns it. This movie is something you could and can be only imagined. And if you then told someone about it they&#39;d have you locked up for a very long time. It could be categorized as a Sci-fi thriller and then as a serial killer film. Like Seven and Silence of the Lambs this is not the ordinary serial killer film. It stands on it&#39;s own as a new kind of thriller.||Jennifer Lopez stars as Catherine Deane, the best psychotherapist in the business. She works for a company who has developed the latest technology in therapy. She has the ability to go inside the mind of anyone and find out the reasoning to his or her distress. Enter Peter Novak (Vince Vaughn), a FBI agent tracking down a very sick serial killer Carl Stargher (Vincent D&#39;Onofrio), who drowns his victims then dresses them up like dolls. On a FBI raid of his home Stargher goes into a coma and the whereabouts of his next victim are unknown. So Deane takes the job of going into his mind to find out where the victim is being held. And that&#39;s when this film gets intense, seriously intense.||The director Tarsem Singh, known for the award winning R.E.M. video `Losing my Religion&#39;, blows away everything you could have imagined. The dream sequences are beautifully shot with many camera tricks, creepy color distribution, graphic images, and a tense score. They are extremely trippy and surreal. They actually have a dream feel because anything goes and there are no rules. Lopez performance is as good as she looks. She nails the psychotherapist dead on and does a great job in showing the different aspects of her character. Vince is Vince, very cool, very low key, and very real. D&#39;Onofrio will scare you. His Carl Stargher would make even Hannibal Lecter scream for mommy. This guy is more disturbed than ever imagined. He has to be seen to believe it.||Tarsem, with this film, has become one of my favorite directors and I will go see any film with his name on it. The Cell can only be described as a Sci-fi serial killer thriller that&#39;s visually disturbing, creepy, and one of the wildest films ever. It runs along the line with Seven for a good serial killer film and Event Horizon for a graphically sick and twisted film. This is best summer movie and the best film I&#39;ve seen all year " VideoFormat="DivX 4" VideoBitrate="784" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="128" Resolution="720x272" Framerate="29,97" Languages="Перевод,English отдельно" Size="697" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\CellXXengX.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="6" Checked="True" Date="23.11.2001" Rating="6.0" OriginalTitle="Bounce" TranslatedTitle="Чужой билет / Билет в один конец / Случайная встреча" FormattedTitle="Bounce (Чужой билет / Билет в один конец / Случайная встреча)" Director="Don Roos" Country="USA" Category="Drama" Year="2000" Length="106" Actors="Ben Affleck (as Buddy Amaral), Gwyneth Paltrow (as Abby Janello), Natasha Henstridge (as Mimi Prager), Edward Edwards (as Ron Wachter), Jennifer Grey (as Janice Guerrero), Tony Goldwyn (as Greg Janello), Lisa Carpenter-Prewitt (as Carol Wilson), Lisa Joyner (as T.V. Announcer), Richard Saxton (as CNN Reporter), Caroline Aaron (as Donna), David Dorfman (I) (as Joey Janello), Alex D. Linz (as Scott Janello), Juan Garcнa (IV) (as Kevin Walters), Mary Ellen Lyon (as Ellen Seitz), Joe Morton (as Jim Willer)" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Title?0186894" Description="Бадди Эмарал (Эффлек), совладелец рекламного агенства, Грегг Джанелло (Голдуин), начинающий писатель, и белокурая красотка (Хенстридж) разговорились за столиком бара в аэропорту, так как вылеты задерживались из-за снегопада. Бадди понравилась девушка, и он отдал свой билет Греггу, а сам вместе с Хенстридж пошел в отель аэропорта, где наутро узнал, что самолет, на котором он должен был лететь, разбился, а все пассажиры и экипаж погибли. А Грегга ждала дома жена Эбби (Пэлтроу), дети. Больше года Бадди был в тяжелейшем состоянии, но все-таки сумел прийти в себя и даже бросил пить. Ему приходит в голову мысль навестить вдову Грегга, и вот он уже стучится в ее дверь. В результате знакомства ротвеллер Эбби порвал костюм Бадди, а Бадди узнал, что Эбби с мужем &#34;развелась&#34; по согласию, работает риэлтером и одна растит детей. Еще через несколько дней Бадди позвонил ей и сделал предложение по работе, которое могло принести ей кучу денег. Выгодная сделка состоялась, а Эбби продолжает говорить о муже, как о живом. Неожиданно она заходит к нему в офис и приглашает на игру &#34;Доджерс&#34;, желая отблагодарить. Со временем Бадди понимает, что его порыв помочь вдове человека, который, как он считает, погиб вместо него, превращается в нечто большее. Не знавший поражений у женщин, Бадди влюбляется в Эбби по-настоящему, как взрослый мужчина. Но теперь надо как-то сказать правду...||Конечно, это предсказуемая, но очень трогательная мелодрама. Эффлек и Пэлтроу играют убедительно, передавая тончайшие нюансы человеческих чувств. Иногда так полезно посмотреть добрый, бесхитростный фильм, дающий иллюзию надежды на лучшее. Бывает, что надежды сбываются.  (Иванов М.)" Comments="The plot of this movie is so difficult to believe, that I was just shaking my head as I watch the plot unfold.  The pace is very slow, and you want to give &#34;Bounce&#34; a kick-start. If you can get over Ben Affleck&#39;s bad acting in this movie you wil see that this movie&#39;s plot has no sense of reality. Gwyneth Paltrow is wonderful as usual and is the only bright spot in this movie. I&#39;ve seen other comments describing this as a &#34;date movie&#34;.  Far from it. It is depressing, and totally unbelieveable. You can do so much better with many other Affleck or Paltrow films " VideoFormat="DivX 4" VideoBitrate="696" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="96" Resolution="624x304" Framerate="25" Languages="Закадровый перевод 1 голос,English отдельно" Size="615" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\BounceXXengX.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="7" Checked="True" Date="14.06.2003" Rating="7.0" OriginalTitle="Cast Away" TranslatedTitle="Изгой / Робинзон" FormattedTitle="Cast Away (Изгой / Робинзон)" Director="Robert Zemeckis" Country="USA" Category="Adventure" Year="2000" Length="140" Actors="Tom Hanks (as Chuck Noland), Helen Hunt (as Kelly Frears), Nick Searcy (as Stan), Chris Noth (as Jerry Lovett), Lari White (as Bettina Peterson), Geoffrey Blake (as Maynard Graham), Jenifer Lewis (as Becca Twig), David Allen Brooks (as Dick Peterson), Semion Suradikov (as Nicolai), Nan Martin (as Kelly&#39;s Mother), Peter von Berg (as Yuri), Dmitri S. Boudrine (as Lev), Leonid Citer (as Fyodor), Anne Bellamy (as Anne Larson), Dennis Letts (as Dennis Larson)" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Title?0162222" Description="Чак Нолан, работник московского отделения скоростной доставки &#34;Федерал Эксрпесс&#34;, должен вскоре жениться на своей любимой девушки Хелен Хант, но во время одного из рейсов самолет, на котором он летит, совершает вынужденную посадку на воду. Каким-то чудом при помощи надувного спасательного плотика Чаку удается спастись. Ему, как современному &#34;робинзону&#34; приходится провести пять долгих лет на необитаемом острове. Смотреть за тем, как Нолан делает все только ради выживания, уже крайне интересно, а вот дождется ли его любимая девушка, это Вы сможете узнать сами. Прекрасно снятый и захватывающий фильм.||&#34;Оскарные&#34; номинации за лучшую мужскую роль Тому Хэнксу, звук,  (Иванов М.)" Comments="CAST AWAY / (2000) *** (out of four) ||By Blake French:||(this comment on &#34;Cast Away&#34; does contain material of a spoiling nature).||&#34;Cast Away&#34; starts on a fairly entertaining note, but devolves into a contrived love story and becomes buried in tedious sequences in which its characters have nothing to do. The main character spends most of the movie&#39;s dreadfully long running time alone on a desolate island-but we determined from trailers and TV ads that the character is retrieved after four years, which kind of eliminates the tension of whether or not he will get off the island alive. ||Tom Hanks plays Nick Noland, a systems engineer for Federal Express who intends to wed his long time girlfriend, Kelley (Helen Hunt), after he returns from a business trip over the south Pacific. We are not surprised when his plane encounters a horrible storm. During one of the most intensely convincing crash sequences ever made, the aircraft plummets into the ocean below, miles off course. Nick is the sole survivor, finding a resting place on a deserted tropical island. Time passes, he builds shelter, losses hope, but nonetheless survives.  If you are not aware of his eventual rescue after four years, then you are not among the movies target audience. The story really focuses on Nick starting his life over and overcoming extreme odds. He finds out that Kelley became married and the rest of society has assumed his death. Nick&#39;s determination is encouraging, but the movie needs more detailing survival on the island. The scenes on the island are the movies best. The film is very careful not to become idle. There are constantly new situations and conflicts being introduced, even though their scenes are often slow moving and tedious. ||Tom Hanks does an exceptional job as the only real character in the film, all other&#39;s are plot devices. There are a few attempts to introduce side characters, but in a movie like this that is nearly impossible, although the actors do a reasonable job with what little screen time they behold.||Director Robert Zemekis stays focused on a consistent narrative instead of going back and forth between characters, like the mediocre &#34;Six Days, Seven Nights.&#34; This is a thought-provoking situation, but most of us already know how the plot concludes. The actual conclusion itself is actually dissatisfying and inconclusive. &#34;Cast Away&#34; is still a good production, well made, and beautifully crafted. I liked the directors consistent style and focused narrative, the plane crash sequence, and I give the film a marginal recommendation " VideoFormat="DivX 3.11 Low Motion" VideoBitrate="1269" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="112" Resolution="640x352" Framerate="24,021" Languages="Перевод" Size="691+689" Disks="2" Picture="Covers\CastXaway.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="8" Checked="True" Date="21.09.2003" Rating="8.0" OriginalTitle="Braveheart" TranslatedTitle="Храброе сердце" FormattedTitle="Braveheart (Храброе сердце)" Director="Mel Gibson" Country="USA" Category="Drama" Year="1995" Length="174" Actors="Mel Gibson (as William Wallace), James Robinson (II) (as Young William), Sean Lawlor (as Malcolm Wallace), Sandy Nelson (II) (as John Wallace), James Cosmo (as Campbell), Sean McGinley (as MacClannough), Alan Tall (as Elder Stewart), Andrew Weir (as Young Hamish), Gerda Stevenson (as Mother MacClannough), Ralph Riach (as Priest No. 1), Mhairi Calvey (as Young Murron), Brian Cox (as Argyle Wallace), Patrick McGoohan (as Longshanks - King Edward I), Peter Hanly (as Prince Edward), Sophie Marceau (as Princess Isabelle)" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Title?0112573" Description="Есть 1 дисковая версия|Действие этого широкомасштабного фильма, чем-то напоминающего &#34;Спартак&#34;, начинается в 1280 год в Шотландии. Мы узнаем историю легендарного национального героя Уильяма Уолласа, посвятившего себя борьбе с англичанами при короле Эдварде Длинноногом. Он рано лишился отца, погибшего от рук англичан, и его забрал к себе дядя Оргайл, который дал ему хорошее образование в Европе. На Родину Уильям возвращается уже взрослым человеком (Гибсон), мечтающим завести семью и жить мирной жизнью. Но судьба распорядилась иначе. Его невесту убили англичане, и он начал свой крестовый поход за свободу. Он знал победы, поражения, дружбу, любовь и предательство. Заканчивается фильм его казнью под пытками и последним словом &#34;свобода&#34;. Нигде в кино я не видел еще так великолепно сделанных батальных сцен. Некоторые могут счесть их излишне жестокими, но вряд ли они могут быть более жестокими, чем это было в реальности. &#34;Оскары&#34; за лучшую картину, режиссуру, операторскую работу, грим (Питер Фрэмптон, Пол Пэттисон, Луис Беруэлл), звуковые эффекты (Лон Бендер и Пер Холлберг). Номинции за лучший оригинальный сценарий, лучшие костюмы, монтаж, музыкальное, драматическое сопровождение, звук.  (Иванов М.)" Comments="Congratulations to all concerned with the making of this excellent film.  I can only think of words of praise. The background set in the highlands of Scotland with its gripping scenery in the barbaric 13th Century brought both the realism and conditions under which people who lived in those times had to endure.  The film did not rely on gimmicks, but pure storyline and professional acting.  Even the brutality of mediaeval warfare was handled with accuracy and not used to shock but to portray reality. Essentially based on the power of love,freedom and national pride, Mel Gibson takes the character from the boy who sees his father killed, his new wife murdered and his country controlled by a foreign power through Scottish nobles who were only concerned at protecting their own selfish interests and survival. For me it was the last scene when Wallace endures public torture and death before giving up his principle - the importance of Freedom which embodies everything that drives the human spirit.  Again an excellent film.  This is what film making should be about.  I look forward to seeing the sequel " VideoFormat="DivX 5" VideoBitrate="1132" AudioFormat="AC3" AudioBitrate="448" Resolution="640x304" Framerate="23,976" Languages="Закадровый перевод 1 голос" Size="674+676+640" Disks="3" Picture="Covers\Braveheart.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="9" Checked="True" Date="13.12.2001" Rating="6.0" OriginalTitle="Acid House, The" TranslatedTitle="Кислотный дом" FormattedTitle="Acid House, The (Кислотный дом)" Director="Paul McGuigan (I)" Country="UK" Category="Drama" Year="1998" Length="112" Actors="Stephen McCole (as Boab (The Granton Star Case)), Maurice Roлves (as God (The Granton Star Case)/Drunk (A Soft Touch)/Priest (The Acid House)), Garry Sweeney (as Kev (The Granton Star Case)), Jenny McCrindle (as Evelyn (The Granton Star Case)), Simon Weir (as Tambo (The Granton Star Case)), Iain Andrew (as Grant (The Granton Star Case)), Irvine Welsh (as Parkie (The Granton Star Case)), Pat Stanton (as Barman (The Granton Star Case)), Alex Howden (as Boab Snr (The Granton Star Case)), Annie Louise Ross (as Doreen (The Granton Star Case) (as Ann Louise Ross)), Dennis O&#39;Connor (III) (as PC Cochrane (The Granton Star Case)), John Gardner (IX) (as Sgt. Morrison (The Granton Star Case)), William Blair (as Workmate (The Granton Star Case)/Deck (A Soft Touch)), Gary McCormack (as Workmate (The Granton Star Case)/Larry (A Soft Touch)), Malcolm Shields (as Workmate (The Granton Star Case))" URL="http://us.imdb.com/Tsearch?title=Acid+House%2C+The+%281998%29" Description="По мотивам рассказов сборника &#34;Кислотый дом&#34; Ирвина Уэлша.||В первой новелле молодой парень Боб плохо играет в футбольном матче, и его выгоняют из команды. Родители говорят, что ему пора жить отдельно. Парня увольняют с работы, он узнает, что его девушка нашла себе другого. В баре он встречает... Бога в виде обычного мужчины лет 45, который, считая Боба ничтожеством, превращает его в... муху. Став мухой, Боб узнает много неожиданного и неприятного о своих друзьях и родителях-извращенцах. Однажды мать убивает его мухобойкой.||В новелле &#34;Джонни и Катрина&#34; зритель знакомится с самой отвратной и распутной стервой, изменяющей при ребенке своему молодому мужу с соседом. Забеременев от него (он прогоняет ее), Катрина возвращается к безответному Джонни, и тот безропотно принимает ее обратно.||В третьей новелле молодой панк Колин Брайт по кличке Коко в результате атмосферного разряда электричества поменялся сознанием с младенцем, только что родившимся в карете &#34;Скорой помощи&#34;. В итоге большого Коко с сознанием младенца, &#34;лепит&#34;, как из глины, в соответствии со своими желаниями юная беременная невеста, а сам Коко берет под каблук свою &#34;мамашу&#34;, с удовольствием сосет ее пышную грудь и заставляет ходить по барам...||Все три новеллы о низшем классе провинциальной Шотландии пропитаны чернушной грубостью, насилием, жестокостью и бездуховностью. Весь коктейль фильма замешан на сексе, пьянстве и наркотиках. Смотреть его было бы совершенно неприятно, если бы порой не проскальзывало сострадание...  (Иванов М.)" Comments="Irvine Welsh&#39;s follow up to Trainspotting hits the screen as three short stories set in Edinburgh, all with a few of Welsh&#39;s trade marks, drug culture, depression, the working class and Hibernian football club. Uneasy to watch in places, it is no less than very well written, 2 of the stories having a darkly comic twist to them while the 2nd story a serious (and shockingly realistic) plot to it. Will not appeal to most, including myself to a point,  but will no doubt adopt a cult following " VideoFormat="DivX 3.11 Low Motion" VideoBitrate="829" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="96" Resolution="512x302" Framerate="25" Languages="Перевод" Size="685" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\AcidXHouse.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="10" Checked="True" Date="20.10.2005" OriginalTitle="Buttman&#39;s Big Butt Eurobabes #21" TranslatedTitle="ХХХ Buttman&#39;s Big Butt Eurobabes #21" FormattedTitle="Buttman&#39;s Big Butt Eurobabes #21 (ХХХ Buttman&#39;s Big Butt Eurobabes #21)" Category="Adult" Length="139" VideoFormat="DivX 5" VideoBitrate="640" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="64" Resolution="416x320" Framerate="25" Languages="Не требуется" Size="700" Disks="1"/>
   <Movie Number="11" Checked="True" Date="03.10.2005" Rating="4.7" OriginalTitle="Ilsa, the Wicked Warden / Greta - Haus ohne Menner / Greta the Torturer / Greta, the Mad Butcher / Greta, the Sadist / Ilsa: Absolute Power / Wanda, the Wicked Warden" TranslatedTitle="Ильза, злая надзирательница / Грета - дом без мужчин/ Грета, безумный мясник/ Грета, палач / Грета, садистка / Ванда, злая надзирательница / Ильза, абсолютная власть / Ильза, абсолютная пытка" FormattedTitle="Ilsa, the Wicked Warden / Greta - Haus ohne Menner / Greta the Torturer / Greta, the Mad Butcher / Greta, the Sadist / Ilsa: Absolute Power / Wanda, the Wicked Warden (Ильза, злая надзирательница / Грета - дом без мужчин/ Грета, безумный мясник/ Грета, палач / Грета, садистка / Ванда, злая надзирательница / Ильза, абсолютная власть / Ильза, абсолютная пытка)" Director="Jesus Franco" Producer="Erwin C. Dietrich , Jesus Franco" Country="USA" Category="Horror" Year="1977" Length="92" Actors="Dyanne Thorne (as Greta), Tania Busselier (as Abbie Phillips), Eric Falk, Lina Romay (as Juana), Esther Studer, Esther Moser, Peggy Markoff, Sandra L. Brennan, Alex Exler, Jesus Franco (as Dr. Milton Arcos (as Jess Franco)), Howard Maurer, Angela Ritschard" URL="http://imdb.com/title/tt0076112" Description="Латинская Америка, 1970-е годы. Ильза (она же Грета, она же Ванда) - надзирательница в женской исправительной тюрьме, подвергает их пыткам. После бунта заключенные разрывают ее на части:" Comments="&#39;A notorious sleaze-series and I&#39;m not involved?!?:That simply cannot be&#39;, Franco must have thought while watching the previous Ilsa installments. And so he filmed his very own addition to what is perhaps the most infamous exploitation series ever made. Ilsa, portrayed by the blouse-bursting wench Dyanne Thorne, appears any place where vicious, nasty events occur:Nazi experiment camps (still the most shocking film in the series), Mid-Eastern harems and Siberian torturing camps. In Franco&#39;s vile fantasies, she runs an American hospital for deranged women. Although that&#39;s merely just a cover-up, because in the deepest cellars of this institution political rebels are imprisoned. When a young girl goes undercover to find out what really happened to her supposedly dead sister, she gets institutionalized and discovers that the hospital is a Sodom and Gomorrah of perverted lesbian guards and sexually insane inmates. Masochism, rape and torturing are a daily routine. None of the Ilsa movies were ever great:but at least the first two had several extra values that made them legendary. She Wolf of the SS was nauseating and downright shocking. Harem keeper of the oil sheiks inserted bizarre and absurd humor. Tigress of Siberia and this Wicked Warden have nothing to add, really. An hour and a half of pure perversion and European class-A sleaze. Dyanne Thorne is clearly getting older and her sexual charisma seems to have vanished entirely. She&#39;s a redhead now, by the way. Fans of the previous installments might still enjoy this film as well as devoted Thorne fans. All other audiences will simply see this is as a lame variant on the &#39;Babes behind Bars&#39;-flicks." VideoFormat="DivX 5" VideoBitrate="954" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="96" Resolution="720x416" Framerate="23,976" Languages="English" Size="691" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\Ilsa, the Wicked Warden.jpg"/>
   <Movie Number="12" Checked="True" Date="11.01.2005" Rating="4.0" OriginalTitle="Buttcrack / Troma&#39;s ButtCrack (Troma)" TranslatedTitle="# Buttcrack" FormattedTitle="Buttcrack / Troma&#39;s ButtCrack (Troma) (# Buttcrack)" Director="Jim Larsen" Country="USA" Category="Comedy" Year="1998" Length="66" Actors="Doug Ciskowski (as Brian), Caleb Kreischer (as Wade &#39;Buttcrack&#39; Jenkins), Rob Hayward (as Ken), Kathy Wittes (as Annie), Kris Arnold (as Trevor), Cindy Geary (as Wade&#39;s Sister), Mojo Nixon (as Preacher Man Bob)" URL="http://imdb.com/title/tt0191019" Description="The gun-totin&#39;, Bible-thumpin&#39; Preacher Man Bob must right the universal karma accidently set wrong when Brian inadvertantlty kills his obnoxious butt-cleavaged roommate, Wade." VideoFormat="XviD" VideoBitrate="863" AudioFormat="MPEG Layer 3 (MP3)" AudioBitrate="112" Resolution="352x288" Framerate="23,976" Languages="English" Size="460" Disks="1" Picture="Covers\Buttcrack (Troma&#39;s ButtCrack).jpg"/>
  </Contents>
 </Catalog>
</AntMovieCatalog>
